

LINKS

• Portfolio: axydavid.com

• GitHub: github.com/axydavid

SKILLS

• **Software Developer**: Java, C#, C, C++, and Python Full-stack

• **Web Developer**: React, Express, Node.JS, HTML5, CSS, PHP, SQL, JQuery, Wordpress

• Game Developer: Unity Engine,

Photon Network

LANGUAGES

English: Bilingual
Romanian: Bilingual
Swedish: Advanced
Danish: Conversational
Norwegian: Conversational

DAVID AXINTE Software Developer

Hello!

My main area of expertise is in full-stack development, using React as my choice Web Framework for the frontend and SQL with Express/Node.JS for the back-end.

I developed software solutions for various professionals, entrepreneurs, and SMEs and have acquired the necessary project management experience.

Within my area of responsibility, I had to identify, assess, and create software solutions where analyzing events or data necessitated an in-depth evaluation of variable aspects.

I can act independently to determine methods and procedures for new undertakings; however, I am also open to learning new programming languages and skills.

I am familiar with various operating systems and databases and have the ability to diagnose hardware, software, and network issues.

Given my experience, I have gained excellent interpersonal and communication skills, along with analytical thinking and problem-solving skills.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN IT & COMPUTER SCIENCE

Technical University of Denmark| Grad. 2018

- Extra specialization in hardware programming
- Extensive experience with game development

AWARDS

REACT DEVELOPER CERTIFICATION

W3School

• Completed W3School necessary courses and exams.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE CONSULTANT

TotalReward | 2020 - 2021

I had to design and maintain a system seamlessly aiding direct sellers and distributors throughout the sales and marketing process providing features that assist with lead generation, marketing, customer management, inventory, and distribution. I was also supposed to manage the team ensuring a swift and reliable development. I used jQuery, JS, HTML5, CSS for front-end and PHP, SQL for back-end.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

UB University | 2019 - 2020

Designed a platform facilitating online exams, tests and practice. Implemented as a web application it was collecting the student responses and gave relevant analytics to the teacher. It also had an algorithm that could, based on the available data give relevant suggestions to both the teacher and the students on how to improve their respective weak areas within their subjects. I used ¡Query, JS, HTML5, CSS for front-end and PHP, SQL for back-end.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

YourPhoner | 2018

Had to develop a website and integrate some CRM. I used the WordPress platform for prototyping along with jQuery, JS, HTML5, CSS and PHP.

OTHER PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GAME DEVELOPER

PortaPlay | 2017 - 2018

Developed and implemented a complete multiplayer experience for an existing game in the Unity engine using C#. Synchronized multiple clients using the photon engine framework.

ANDROID APP DEVELOPER

LinkBus | 2017

Developed an android application for an electric car. It can track various parameters such as time, speed, battery, RPM, etc., and uses an algorithm with that data to make predictions such as KM or time left before the battery will be empty.